(tires screech)
(upbeat music)
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ First time was a great time ♪
♪ Second time was a blast ♪
♪ Third time I fell in love ♪
♪ Now I hope it lasts ♪
♪ I can see it in your walk ♪
♪ Tell it when you talk ♪
♪ See it in everything you do ♪
♪ Even in your thoughts ♪
♪ You got the right stuff, baby ♪
♪ Love the way you turn me on ♪
♪ You're the reason why I sing this song ♪
♪ All that I needed was you ♪
♪ Oh girl, you're so right ♪
♪ Said all that I wanted was you ♪
♪ You made all my dreams come true ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Your first kiss was a sweet kiss ♪
♪ Second kiss had a twist ♪
♪ Third and your fourth kiss ♪
♪ I don't want to miss ♪
♪ I can see it in your walk ♪
♪ Tell it when you talk ♪
♪ See it in everything you do ♪
♪ Even in your thoughts ♪
♪ You got the right stuff, baby ♪
♪ Love the way you turn me on ♪
♪ You're the reason why I sing this song ♪
♪ All that I needed was you in my life ♪
♪ You're so right ♪
♪ Said all that I wanted was you ♪
♪ You made all every one
of my dreams come true ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Girl, yeah baby, yeah ♪
♪ You know you got the right stuff ♪
♪ And girl, yeah, baby ♪
♪ You know, you know you got it, girl ♪
♪ In my life, you're so right ♪
♪ You made all, you know what you did ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ The right stuff ♪
♪ You got the right stuff, baby ♪
♪ Love the way you turn me on ♪
♪ You're the reason why I sing this song ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh ♪